Guide to the Adil Jussawalla papers, 1944-2016
Jussawalla, Adil papers
- Assorted Files, 1965-1992
  - Frankfurt Bookfair Information, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
Mehrotra, Arvind Krishna. Distance in Statute Miles
Lal, P. The Parrot's Death and Other Poems
de Souza, Eunice. Women in Dutch Painting
Patel, Gieve. How Do You Withstand, Body
Jussawalla, Adil. Missing Person
Patel, Gieve. Mister Behram
Mistry, Cyrus. Doongaji House
Shetty, Manohar. Borrowed Time
Shivdasani, Menka. Nirvana at Ten Rupees
Lal, P. Love's the First
Rehman, Tariq. Work and other Short Stories
Vatsyayana, S. H. Prison Days and Other Poems
Khabardar, Ardeshir F. The Silken Tassel
Jhabvala, S. H. Poems: Written in Prison
Sett, Adi K. Rain in My Heart
Chander, Krishan. Seven Faces of London
Malgonkar, Manohar. Bombay Beware
Rahman, Tariq. A History of Pakistani Literature in English
Fernandes, Keith and Eunice de Souza (Editors). Bequest
Opinion Literary Quarterly Winter Issue
Opinion Literary Quarterly Autumn Issue
Opinion Literary Quarterly Spring Issue
Dhondy, Farrukh and Diane Troy. Carcanet
Measure 3: Young Poets of India,
Nandy, Pritish (Translator). Poems from Bangladesh
Anstey, F. Baboo Jabberjee
Katrak, K. D. Purgatory: Songs from The Holy Planet
Chattopadhyaya, Harindranath. The Map of the World
Banerjea, Pradeep (Translator). Some Post-Independence Bengali Poems
Shungloo, Krishan. The Night is Heavy
Chattopadhyaya, Harindranath. The Sleeper Awakened
Chattopadhyaya, Harindranath. Edgeways and the Saint
Jhabvala, S. H. Kabir
Acharya, Sri Ananda. Snow-Birds
Malgonkar, Manohar. Rumble-Tumble
Katrak, K. D. A Journal of the Way
Katrak, K. D. Diversions by the Waysidee
Sen, Pradip. And then the Sun
Katrak, K. D. Underworld
Tripathi, Govardhanram Madhavram. Scrap Book
Trivikram, T. K. N. Zero B.C. or Christ-Upanishad
Hutheesing, Krishna. With No Regrets
Pillai, G. Parameswaran. London and Paris through Indian Spectacles
Kohli, Devindra (Editor). Indian Writers at Work